{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question":"Which of the following JavaScript cannot do?",
      "answers":["JavaScript can react to events","JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements","JavaScript can be use to validate data","All of the Above"],
      "correct":3
   },
   {
       "id": 2,
       "question":"_________ keyword is used to declare variables in javascript.",
       "answers":["Var","Dim","String"],
       "correct":0
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question":"The attribute used to define a new namespace is.",
      "answers":["XMLNS","XmlNameSpace","Xmlns","XmlNs"],
      "correct":2
   },
   {
    "id": 4,
    "question":"Which browser can supports the transition property?",
    "answers":["Internet Explorer 10","Firefox","Chrome","All of the Above"],
    "correct":3
 },
 {
  "id": 5,
  "question":"Which of the following options is correct with regard to HTML?",
  "answers":["It is a modelling language","It is a scripting language","It is a partial programming language","It is used to structure documents"],
  "correct":3
},
{
  "id": 6,
  "question":"Which CSS property can provide to add an effect when changing from one style to another,without using Flash animations or javascript?",
  "answers":["Associations","Transitions","Transistor","None of the above"],
  "correct":1
},
{
  "id": 7,
  "question":"____________ is the tainted property of a window object.",
  "answers":["Pathname","Protocol","Defaultstatus","Host"],
  "correct":2
},
{
  "id": 8,
  "question":"When a JavaScript object is sent to Java, the runtime engine creates a Java wrapper of type",
  "answers":["ScriptObject","JSObject","JavaObject","Jobject"],
  "correct":1
},
{
  "id": 9,
  "question":"The TFOOT section of a table must appear before the TBODY section.",
  "answers":["True","False"],
  "correct":1
},
{
  "id": 10,
  "question":"Which of the following is NOT a Style?",
  "answers":["Linked","Embedded","Inline","Orthogonal"],
  "correct":3
}
  ] 
}